UNITE Northeast Department Files 6000/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Northeast Department Files
1985-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
6000/012
3.33 cubic feet
3.3 linear ft.
Records.
This collection includes files of UNITE, ILGWU, and ACTWU.
5750604
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Nicole Dardia/Casey Westerman, February 29, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/012 AV: UNITE Northeast Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/012 P: UNITE Northeast Department Photographs
Textile industry -- New York (State); Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing trade -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; UNITE HERE (Organization)
5750604
- Ames [folder 1 of 2], 1993-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Ames [folder 2 of 2], 1993-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- AACA - Letter, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Negotiations (AACA), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- AACA Contracts, 1985-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Atlantic Apparel Negotiations, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Scope and Contents
  January 24
- Original AACA Contract, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  February
- Calvin Klein / Kai Jay, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Dante Fashions, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Debbi-Sue Fashions, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Delta Dental of Pennsylvania, 1987-1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- T.G. Faust, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Gateway Sportswear, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- M.I. Huebschman Co., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Jensporsts Agreement, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- K-mart [folder 1 of 2], 1985-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- K-mart [folder 2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Kelley Avenue Public Warehouse Contract, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Krisport, Inc., 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Lady Hope Dress Company, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Lawrence Children's Underwear Co. and Donegal Industries, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- LDP (Leadership Data Processing), 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Leslie Fay [folder 1 of 4], 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Leslie Fay [folder 2 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Leslie Fay [folder 3 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Leslie Fay [folder 4 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Leslie Fay [folder 1 of 2], 1994-1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Leslie Fay [folder 2 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Leslie Fay, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Linden Apparel, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Atlantic Apparel, Northeast Apparel Association, Liz Claiborne, 1985-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Liz Claiborne [folder 1 of 2], 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Liz Claiborne [folder 2 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Liz Claiborne - Negotiation Notes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Liz Claiborne [folder 1 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Liz Claiborne [folder 2 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Jay Mazur - Liz Claiborne Materials, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Liz Claiborne [folder 1 of 2], 1990-1995 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Liz Claiborne [folder 2 of 2], 1990-1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- North American Knitting Company, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- North American Knitting Company Folder 2, 1993-1998 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Penn-Tex, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Phillips Van Heusen [folder 1 of 2], 1990-1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Phillips Van Heusen [folder 2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 3)
- PAC (Political Action Committee), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Poughkeepsie Finishing Corporation (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Rossmor Industries, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Zip-Net Inc., 1997-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR) [folder 1 of 2], 1994-1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- FOUR [folder 2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Major Market Negotiations - Sol Hoffman, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- David Melman American Express, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- David Melman - Paid Reimbursement Statements, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- David Melman - Paid Vouchers, 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Vouchers, Paid [folder 1 of 2], 1995-1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Vouchers, Paid [folder 2 of 2], 1995-1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- UNITE Misc. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- UNITE Misc. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Unite Misc. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Retirement Party: Celetino's Restaurant, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  September 12, 1996.
- Local 295 Signs, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Leslie Fay mail-in cards (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Newspaper supplement on Scranton Anniversary (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Leslie Fay campaign bumper stickers (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Nail files (Political campaign) (Box 4, Folder 4)